export const basicQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Define components in VueJS.",
    answer: ["Modular Vue instances designed for reusability."],
    options: [
      "Modular Vue instances designed for reusability.",
      "JavaScript functions that structure HTML elements.",
      "CSS styles applied exclusively to Vue templates.",
      "Database queries embedded in Vue applications.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 15,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "How can components be created in Vue?",
    answer: ["The Vue component is placed in a single dedicated file using the `.vue` extension.", "The Vue component can be defined as a plain JavaScript object containing Vue-specific options."],
    options: [
      "Utilizing the newComponent() method.",
      "Declaring a Vue instance with Vue.createComponent().",
      "The Vue component is placed in a single dedicated file using the `.vue` extension.",
      "The Vue component can be defined as a plain JavaScript object containing Vue-specific options.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 20,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What purpose do Props serve in Vue?",
    answer: ["Custom attributes transferred from parent to child components."],
    options: [
      "HTML tags within Vue templates.",
      "Variables confined to the created lifecycle hook.",
      "Custom attributes transferred from parent to child components.",
      "Internal state management variables in Vue instances.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 15,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Explain the data flow between Vue components.",
    answer: ["Unidirectional data flow from parent to child through props and child to parent via events."],
    options: [
      "Bidirectional data flow solely from child to parent components.",
      "Unidirectional data flow from parent to child through props and child to parent via events.",
      "Limited data flow confined to components within the same hierarchy.",
      "Data flow occurs arbitrarily based on component rendering order.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 25,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What are slots in the context of Vue?",
    answer: ["Reserved areas in templates designated for dynamic content."],
    options: [
      "Reserved areas in templates designated for dynamic content.",
      "Special Vue components exclusively for rendering images.",
      "Keywords reserved for conditional rendering.",
      "External libraries specifically for Vue animations.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 15,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "How can fallback content be added for slots in Vue?",
    answer: ["Providing default content within the slot tags."],
    options: [
      "Using the slot-fallback attribute.",
      "Providing default content within the slot tags.",
      "Employing the v-fallback directive.",
      "Fallback content is not supported for slots in Vue.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 20,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What do attribute bindings refer to in Vue?",
    answer: ["Dynamically updating HTML attributes based on Vue data."],
    options: [
      "Linking external CSS files to Vue components.",
      "Dynamically updating HTML attributes based on Vue data.",
      "Assigning static values to HTML attributes.",
      "Creating custom attributes for Vue templates.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 15,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "How is a two-way binding achieved in Vue?",
    answer: ["By using the v-model directive.", "Manually implement by emitting and listening to the input event."],
    options: [
      "Employing the v-two-way directive.",
      "By using the v-model directive.",
      "Manually implement by emitting and listening to the input event.",
      "By using the v-bind directive.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 20,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Define directives in the context of Vue.",
    answer: ["Special tokens in HTML attributes triggering reactive behavior."],
    options: [
      "External scripts imported into Vue components.",
      "Special tags used for conditional rendering.",
      "Custom methods for data manipulation in Vue instances.",
      "Special tokens in HTML attributes triggering reactive behavior.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 15,
    points: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Can multiple values be passed to a directive in Vue?",
    answer: ["Yes, using an array or an object to pass multiple values."],
    options: [
      "Yes, separating values with commas within the directive.",
      "Yes, using an array or an object to pass multiple values.",
      "Yes, repeating the directive for each value.",
      "No, directives only accept a single value.",
    ],
    timeToAnswer: 20,
    points: 1,
  },
];
